Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6; 22929
  - Events, 2009 May 16-2016 July 14; 6.1; 22929
    - President: 2/2/06 @ 12 Noon President's Office Joe Bowman and Johanna Duncan-Portier, 2006 February 16; 18.5 MB 9
    - Alumni Affairs: 6/2/06 @ 6 PM Desmond Hotel Latham Gala Awards / Alumni Weekend, 2006 February 20; 206.9 MB 99
    - Alumni Affairs: 6/3/06 @ Various times and locations class portraits, 2006 February 20; 461.6 MB 197
    - Advancement: 2/17/06 @ 9:15 AM Cancer Research Center various lab shots, 2006 March 3; 358.8 MB 179
    - Alumni Affairs: 3/2/06 @ 9 AM Alumni House UAlbany apparel, 2006 March 14; 129.9 MB 22
    - President: 3/6/06 @ 9 AM location TBA Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; 112.1 MB 56
    - President: 3/6/06 @ Noon location TBA Board of Visitors Luncheon, 2006 March 16; 40.4 MB 15
    - President: 3/7/06 @ 10:45 AM Capital Bldg. Albany SUNY Day, 2006 March 16; 82.9 MB 40
    - President: 3/10/06 Time and location TBA New Jobs NY w/ Hilary Clinton, 2006 March 16; 224.8 MB 105
    - President: 3/12/06 @ time TBA CC President's Leadership Awards Ceremony, 2006 March 16; 394.1 MB 101
    - President: 3/13/06 @ Noon - 1:30 PM CC (Ballroom or Assembly Hall) Minority Scholars Lunch for Albany High, 2006 March 16; 61.9 MB 30
    - President: 3/20/06 @ 2:30 PM Life Science Bldg Presentations for Board of Visitors, 2006 March 16; 48.9 MB 26
    - President: 3/20/06 @ 5:45 PM Milne 200 Board of Visitors (full group) Dinner, 2006 March 16; 128.8 MB 63
    - President: 3/22/06 @ 1:30 PM Standish Room Joe Persico Press Conference, 2006 March 16; 97.1 MB 50
    - President: 3/23/06 @ 8 AM - 5 PM location TBA Tracy Kidder / Albany Reading Project, 2006 March 16; 77.1 MB 39
    - President: 3/9/06 @ 3 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Linda Greenhouse class, 2006 March 16; 21.5 MB 10
    - President: 3/23/06 @ 5:30 PM - 8:30 PM Albany Court of Appeals President Hall lecturing / Judge Judith Kaye, 2006 March 16; 306.9 MB 105
    - University Development: 3/3/06 @ 9:30 AM PAC visiting Albany HS students on tour of campus, 2006 March 17; 79.1 MB 40
    - Jewish Studies: 5/3/06 afternoon and evening Hastings-on-Hudson Jewish Studies Celebration Dinner, 2006 March 22; 483.4 MB 203
    - Library: 5/2/06 @ 2 PM - 4 PM Standish Room Bread and Roses Celebration, 2006 April 3; 187.4 MB 89
    - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ 6:30 PM Pres Res Joe Persico Reception, 2006 April 5; 153.6 MB 70
    - President: 3/22/06 @ 11:45 PM Science Library President for a Day_Vincent Porfirio:, 2006 April 5; 14.8 MB 7
    - Advancement: 3/22/06 @ Noon Science Library / Special Archives Conference Room Joe Persico Luncheon, 2006 April 5; 53.3 MB 27
    - President: 3/21/06 @ 6:15 PM Albany H S press conference:, 2006 April 5; 125.7 MB 62
    - Library: 3/24/06 @ 10:30 AM CC Ballroom Africa and the Diaspora: Agents for Change, 2006 April 6; 93.9 MB 44
    - Advancement: 3/29/06 @ 9:30 AM East Campus / Cancer Ctr - Executive Board Rm 3rd Fl check presentation: First Niagara Bank Foundation, 2006 April 6; 81.6 MB 40
    - Sports Information: 5/1/06 @ 5 PM RACC Great Dane Awards, 2006 April 12; 637.0 MB 137
    - Research: 5/30/06 @ 12:15 Life Science Conferece Rm 1143 / 3 PM Life Science / Auditorium Research Colloquium, 2006 April 12; 338.4 MB 77
    - Arts and Sciences: 4/21/06 @ 3:30 PM SS 369 group photo: students, faculty members and Chair, 2006 May 4; 27.0 MB 10
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597
    - President: 4/26/06 @ 8:30 AM President's Office President for a Day: Elizabeth Gray, 2006 May 10; 64.3 MB 31
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597
    - Admissions: 5/9/06 @ 10:15 AM Prof. Yvonne Bland's classroom Jenna and Jessica Ortman: Day in the Life, 2006 May 10; 1.2 GB 597
    - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; 255.8 MB 59
    - Information Technology Services: 5/23/06 @ 9 - 10:30 AM Management Services Bldg staff meeting and group shot, 2006 May 18; 255.8 MB 59
    - President: 5/10/06 @ 6 PM Pres Res Valedictorian Dinner, 2006 May 24; 143.3 MB 48
    - Development Events: 6/3/06 @ 3:45 PM Pres Res President's Club Reception, 2006 June 13; 205.3 MB 96
    - Student Success: 6/12/06 @ Noon - 2 PM Science Library / West Seminar Room Albany High School Student Award Luncheon, 2006 June 14; 112.9 MB 60
    - Advancement: 6/8/06 @ 4 PM location TBA University Council Meeting, 2006 June 15; 137.3 MB 69
    - Media and Marketing: 6/15/06 @ 8 PM Location TBA Special Olympics / Opening Ceremony, 2006 June 16; 616.9 MB 197
    - President: 6/6/06 - 6/7/06 Long Island, NY various locations Roads Scholar Tour / Long Island, 2006 June 22; 2.5 GB 471
    - Advancement: 6/13/06 @ 5:30 PM Nano Fab steps group: Jiangsu (China) visitors, 2006 June 26; 39.8 MB 26
    - President: 6/14/06 @ 11:30 AM Standish Room Laval Delegation, 2006 June 27; 57.9 MB 31
    - Advancement Events`: 6/2/06 @ 8 AM Ft. Orange Club / Albany, NY CEO Breakfast, 2006 July 3; 131.8 MB 52
    - Advancement: s: 7/7/06 Campus Center / Parent's Fountain portraits: Tom Bessette and Cathy Hornberger Fall 2006 UAlbany Magazine, 2006 July 20; 193.3 MB 83
    - Development Events: 8/14/06 @ 5 PM - 7:30 PM Standish Room / Giant's Practice NY Giant's Donor Reception, 2006 July 24; 43.6 MB 47
    - ETAP: 7/25/06 @ 11 AM SUNY Tunes kids doing a recording, 2006 August 8; 341.5 MB 164
    - Sports Information: 7/26/06 @ 11:30 AM Giant's Dutch Quad Lawn Giant's Media Day, 2006 August 9; 157.1 MB 124
    - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; 438.8 MB 229
    - Development Events: 9/21/06 @ 5:30 PM Hall of Springs, Saratoga, NY 2006 Citizen Laureate, 2006 August 10; 438.8 MB 229
    - Business: 9/5/06 @ 12 Noon Parent's Fountain Connections Cover Shot, 2006 August 14; 314.8 MB 65
    - Advancement: 9/18/06 @ 10 AM RACC Kermit Hall Tribute, 2006 October 2; 519.1 MB 229
    - President: Photo Session: 8/14/06 CC Small Fountain President Kermit Hall Memorial, 2006 October 2; 244.5 MB 173
    - President's Office: 10/3/06 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom for Fall Faculty meeting., 2006 October 3; 151.2 MB 82
    - Development: 10/6/06 @ 2:30 pm University Hall 208C (Check presentation of Mr. Jack Davis from Dell to Chris Haile and Deb Read), 2006 October 6; 36.5 MB 19
    - Media & Marketing: 10/16/06 @ 10:30 AM University Hall Atrium; 10:45 AM Brief Program; 11 AM of People touring the building and any outside shot if needed all for University Hall Open House., 2006 October 16; 110.7 MB 57
    - Media & Marketing: 10/18/06 @ 8:30 am at Albany High School for Albany High School Teach Out, 2006 October 18; 20.9 MB 35
    - Center for Autism: 10/18/06 @ 11 AM Desmond Hotel for Autism conference., 2006 October 18; 36.0 MB 18
    - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; 203.9 MB 95
    - Media & Marketing: 10/20/06 @ 12-1:30 pm CC Ballroom for Alumni Awareness Kick off event, 2006 October 19; 203.9 MB 95
    - Development: 10/20/06 @ 2-3:30 Page Hall for Mental Health Forum for SSW 40th Anniversary., 2006 October 20; 71.3 MB 33
    - Development: 10/20/06 @ 4:45 - 5:45 Milne 200 for SSW 40th Anniversary event, 2006 October 20; 149.5 MB 73
    - Media and Marketing: 10/5/06 @ 2 PM UAB Emeritus Center / Ray Ortali, Bill Reese and Toby Clyman, 2006 October 20; 52.7 MB 30
    - Development: 10/21/06 @ 9:30 - 11 am Standish Room for Alumni Weekend event - Presidents Club Champagne Brunch, 2006 October 21; 23.7 MB 72
    - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; 212.8 MB 120
    - Development: 10/25/06 @ 4-8:30 pm NYC for Foundation Board meeting and reception., 2006 October 25; 21.4 MB 61
    - Governmental Public and Media Relations: 10/18/06 @ 10 AM University Hall Atrium for McNulty Press Event / NERFI Dept of Justice Grant, 2006 October 26; 134.8 MB 69
    - NYLARNET: 11/3/06 @ 9:45 - 10:30 AM Campus Center Assembly Hall for Latino Immigration Policy Conference, 2006 November 3; 102.8 MB 53
    - Media & Marketing: 11/1/06 @ 4 PM Emeritus Center (UAB?) for Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2006 November 4; 66.7 MB 38
    - Development: 11/9/06 from 5:30 - 7:30, Art Museum for Donor Recognition Reception., 2006 November 9; 165.5 MB 83
    - Media & Marketing: 11/14/06 @ 1 - 2 PM Patroon Room for photo of Professor Angie Chung and Food for Thought program, 2006 November 14; 32.5 MB 15
    - Development: 11/15/06 from 5:30 - 7:30 pm, Liife Sciences building for Life Sciences Donor Recognition event., 2006 November 15; 24.1 MB 58
    - President's Office: photo shoot: 11/13/06 @ 4:30 PM in Sub-Basement Studio for Holiday Card, 2006 November 15; 150.6 MB 179
    - Media & Marketing: 11/29/06 @ 3 p.m. Art Museum for photo of a dress rehearsal of a performance marking the 35th anniversary of the Women's Studies department at UAlbany, 2006 November 30; 36.9 MB 25
    - Media & Marketing: 12/11/06 @ 10:30 am UNH Atrium for photo of Whitney Sperrazza addressing the prospective student tour., 2006 December 12; 77.7 MB 39
    - Media & Marketing: 12/12/06 @ 8 pm Recording Studios of the Lecture Center Sub-basement for photo of Whitney Sperrazza rehearsing with Serendipity., 2006 December 13; 77.2 MB 42
    - President's Office: 12/13/06 @ 12 Noon Standish Room for photo of Valedictorian Luncheon 12/13/06 @ 2:30 p.m. UNH Atrium for Faculty/staff holiday party, 2006 December 14; 25.4 MB 62
    - Small Business Development: 01/03/07 @ 10 a.m. Goold Orchards 1297 Brookview Station Road, Castleton, NY for photo of company., 2007 January 4; 232.4 MB 105
    - Media & Marketing: 01/11/07 at 2 p.m. UAB 437 for PDP Open House., 2007 January 11; 80.7 MB 40
    - Center for Autism: 2/1 /07 @ 4:00 pm 1535 Western Ave for Center for Autism ribbon cutting. Types of shots needed: pictures of the ribbon cutting, during the reception, of the building out from with our sign, and a picture of the staff with the Dean and Provost. Need photos in both and hi and low res, 2007 February 2; 38.4 MB 106
    - Media & Marketing: 2/2/07 @ 12 - 1:30 PM SEFCU Arena for photo Lee McElroy Contract Signing, 2007 February 2; 39.5 MB 90
    - Chancellor's Office: 3/1/07 @ 11 AM - 1:30 PM Fireside Lounge, Campus Center for Chancellor's Listening Tour, 2007 March 1; 27.5 MB 80
    - Media & Marketing: 4/27/07 @ 10:30 AM UNH Atrium for Design Entry Media Event, 2007 March 6; 45.2 MB 47
    - Provost's Office: 3/7/07 @ 4 PM University Hall Atrium for photos of Susan Herbst shaking hands with students or a group shot of Susan with some students., 2007 March 7; 26.1 MB 60
    - Media & Marketing: 3/15/07 @ 4 - 5 P.M. at the Downtown Campus in Milne 215 for photo of the Campus Book Project Reading Discussion Group, 2007 March 14; 15.7 MB 33
    - Media & Marketing: 3/16/07 @ 12:15 PM Campus Center (exact location tbd) for photos of students watching the UAlbany Basketball v Vermont., 2007 March 16; 62.8 MB 127
    - Media & Marketing: 3/28/07 @ 9 AM corner of Washington & Quail for Safe Corridor Press Event (series of speakers), 2007 March 29; 110.2 MB 99
    - Media & Marketing: 4/20/07 @ 11 a.m. University Hall Atrium for Biodiversity Event announcement., 2007 April 20; 28.2 MB 39
    - PSC: Photo session - picture of new Psych. Services Center Building for inclusion in 2 brochures (job #'s 20004982 and 4983), 2007 April 23; 82.2 MB 124
    - President's Office: 4/17/07 @ 5 PM Small Fountain for Candle Light Vigil., 2007 April 23; 18.2 MB 54
    - Provost: 4/23/07 @ 3 - 5 PM Campus Center Ballroom for Award of Excellence ceremony, 2007 April 23; 21.5 MB 43
    - Alumni Association: Photo Session; various locations for Alumni Weekend_07; email to follow with specific locations and times, 2007 April 24; 383.2 MB 473
    - Media & Marketing: 4/30/07 @ 2:30 PM meet at Standish Room and then photograph as they tour School of Education and Uptown Campus for News in Photos., 2007 April 26; 27.2 MB 55
    - Center for Women in Government: 4/25/07, Campus Center Ballroom for Language Access Conference during the following times: 9 - 10:30 a.m. for Welcome and Keynote 12:30 - 1:30 p.m. for lunch presentation 4:15 - 5:15 p.m for final session, concluding remarks, and full group photo, 2007 April 26; 219.7 MB 150
    - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; 39.1 MB 41
    - Media and Marketing: 4/16/07 @ 3 PN CC Small Fountain Holocaust Rememberance w/ Susan Herbst reading names of survivors, 2007 April 30; 36.2 MB 33
    - Media and Marketing: 4/17/07 @ 11:30 AM 299 Washington Ave Albany, NY Psychological Services Center Re-Opening Celebration, 2007 April 30; 39.1 MB 41
    - Media & Marketing: 5/9/07 @ 5 PM (will confirm) University Hall Atrium for Stone Exhibit event., 2007 May 2; 40.0 MB 70
    - Libraries: 5/3/07 @ 2 - 4 pm Standish Room, Science Library for Bread and Roses event, 2007 May 3; 189.2 MB 101
    - Media & Marketing: 5/14/07 @ 11:45 AM - 1 PM, Marriott Hotel for Citizen Bank check presentation to University., 2007 May 14; 15.8 MB 31
    - Media & Marketing: 6/18 @ 9:15 AM Campus Center, 2nd Floor for Alcohol Summit News Conference with Mayor, Chancellor and Officer in Charge Susan Herbst., 2007 June 18; 86.8 MB 122
    - NEPHLI: 7/17/07 @ 12 Noon Rensselaerville Institute, 2007 July 17; 54.1 MB 138
    - Media & Marketing:; Alumni Awareness luncheon, campus ctr ballroom on Oct. 12th noon - 2 p.m., 2007 August 14; 376.4 MB 186
    - Informatics: MSIS faculty and master students 8/28/07 from 12 - 1:30 p.m. in MILNE 200, just general shots of interaction, 2007 August 31; 24.1 MB 63
    - Media & Marketing: photos in front of small fountain for Kermit Hall's remeberence ceremony, 2007 September 7; 98.5 MB 79
    - Media & Marketing: photos of Chinese ambassador with his group as well as with Susan Herbst on 9/5/07. Event starts at 3 p.m. in UHALL atrium, please arrive earlier since you have a shoot at athletics at 3:45 p.m., 2007 September 13; 23.8 MB 48
    - Media & Marketing: Mara-Tisch field naming on 8/17/07 @ 4 p.m., 2007 September 19; 113.2 MB 139
    - Advancement Events: 10/13/07 from 9:30 - 11:00 a.m. in the Standish Room, Champagne Jazz Brunch., 2007 September 26; 56.4 MB 103
    - Advancement Events: 11/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m.@ the Hall of Springs in Saratoga for the Citizen Laureate Awards., 2007 September 26; 83.0 MB 186
    - Media & Marketing: 9/17/07 @ 1 p.m. in the Assembly Hall to take shot of Steve Kroft talking w/students, then on to the Medallion ceremony in the Fireside lounge @ 2:30 to get shots of him receiving medallion., 2007 September 28; 58.0 MB 111
    - 9/20/07 @ 9 a.m. Apt. 215 Heritage Rd. Apts., go to intersection of route 20 and route 155, turn south on to route 155 and take left to heritage village, go to end of heritage rd. 3 story apt. bldg, apt. 215. call 452-5429 if you need assistance. * Please bring a back drop! * Is looking for a shot of the 11 books he wrote all in one photo., 2007 October 1; 35.0 MB 13
    - University Events: 12/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, Gala honoring Mayor Jennings, 2007 October 25; 252.3 MB 348
    - Media & Marketing: 10/19/07 at 1 p.m. to take photos fof purple path ground breaking ceremony. Location is SEFCU Arena parking lot near Western Ave side., 2007 October 25; 36.8 MB 61
    - Student Success: 10/15/07 at 2:30 p.m for plaque dedication in memory of Kermit Hall. Location is in front of the Science Library bldg (west garden of the podium)., 2007 October 25; 37.6 MB 63
    - University Events: 12/8/07 from 6 - 9 p.m. at the SEFCU Arena, Gala honoring Mayor Jennings, 2007 October 25; 252.3 MB 348
    - University Events: 10/23/07 at 11:30 a.m. at the Cancer Center on the East Campus. Massry Conference Center Dedication and Luncheon. Please get shots of the Massrys w/various people, Sen. Bruno, George Hearst, George Philip and Susan Herbst. Should conclude at 2 pm., 2007 October 25; 38.1 MB 101
    - Media & Marketing: 10/12/07 at 10:00 a.m. Farmer's market on the podium in front of Campus Center. Take shots for news in photos, looking for color, students buying things and activity., 2007 October 26; 25.6 MB 47
    - Small Business Development Center: Photo Session: 10/30/07 @ 11 AM Materials Recovery Company, 1 Monroe St., Troy, NY for photos to include in SBDC Annual Report, 2007 October 30; 27.6 MB 37
    - Media & Marketing: 10/17/07 at 3:30 at Empire Commons to take shot of Matt Ryan and also Matt with Andrei Lapenas. Shot of Matt for home page. Go Green initiative for conserving electrical energy., 2007 October 31; 35.5 MB 80
    - University Events: 10/31/07 from 3 - 5 p.m. for Celebrating Teaching in the D'ambra Auditorium in the life sciences bldg. to take general shots of event., 2007 November 8; 42.8 MB 80
    - Media & Marketing: 10/26/07 from 2:30 - 4 p.m. to take shots of farewell event for Susan Herbst., 2007 November 9; 42.2 MB 36
    - Media & Marketing: 11/7/07 at 11 a.m. at the small fountain to take shots of press conference celebrating John Lowery for his National Award from American Cancer Society., 2007 November 16; 26.9 MB 39
    - Center for Women in Tech & Gov't.: 11/9/07 from 2:45 - 3:45 at the Italian American Community Center to take shots of Women's cargiving forum. Get general shots and shots of panel speakers., 2007 November 21; 29.6 MB 61
    - Media and Marketing: 11/7/07 @ 10 AM CC Lobby RSVP Craft Fair, 2007 November 21; 19.7 MB 23
    - English: 11/9/07 from 9 - 10:30 at the Standish room to take "dynamic" shots of Ecologies of War conference for english web site., 2007 November 21; 9.3 MB 19
    - Development: 11/29/07 @ 12 - 1:30 p.m., Standish Room, Science Library for Valedictorian luncheon. Type of shots needed: general shots of event & students with their professors and a group shot of all the honorees., 2007 November 21; 23.1 MB 50
    - University Events: 11/27/07 from 8 - 9 a.m. in the SEFCU Hall of Fame room to take shots of speakers and crowd for CEO breakfast featuring Lee McElroy., 2007 November 21; 48.3 MB 78
    - Media and Marketing: 11/9/07 @ 11 AM CC Ballroom Welcome for George Philip, 2007 November 23; 8.9 MB 14
    - Provost: photo sesssion: 11/13/07 @ 5 PM UAB 423 Anniversary Celebration of Emeritus Center, 2007 November 28; 12.1 MB 29
    - Media & Marketing: 12/12/07 @ 1:30 at Harriman Campus, Building 3 for news conference., 2007 December 12; 64.9 MB 78
    - Center for Women in Government & Civil: 1/11/08 @ 10:45 AM - 12 Noon, Draper 105 for head shots and a group photo of our Fellows on Women and Public Policy. (Location for group photo could be front of Draper Hall, or perhaps the Dewey Library), 2008 January 12; 78.8 MB 183
    - Media Relations: 1/25/08 @ 1:30 PM Patroon Lounge, for photo of George Philip at Friends exhibit lunch to be used in News in Photo and possible release. Type of shot: George interacting with people or pointing at exhibit with exhibit as backdrop., 2008 January 17; 48.0 MB 62
    - Media & Marketing: 2/8/08 @ 3 PM in LC1 for Darwin Day event., 2008 February 8; 5.4 MB 12
    - Media Relations: 2/7/08 @ 12 Noon, CC Ballroom for Martin Luther King Jr. Event. Speaker: Myrlie Evers-Willilams. Types of shots: speaker at the podium, possibly interacting with UAlbany officials and students., 2008 February 8; 88.4 MB 93
    - Media and Marketing: 2/5/08 @ 8 am HOF room SEFCU Arena Breakfast of Champions, 2008 February 19; 114.3 MB 63
    - Media and Marketing: 2/13/08 @ 11:30 AM Sefcu Arena Job fair / exposition, 2008 February 27; 26.1 MB 53
    - President's Office: 2/27/08 @ 1 PM in UNH 302 (George's Office) for photo of Brandy Barnard - new UPD Officer being sworn in., 2008 February 27; 19.4 MB 27
    - Media and Marketing: Photo Session: 3/3/08, 11:00 AM for Giants sign unveiling:, 2008 March 3; 28.2 MB 50
    - Economics Dept: Photo session: 3/7/08 @ 2:30 - 4:00 @ Economics Dept for Nobel Laureate Robert Engle., 2008 March 7; 25.1 MB 52
    - Media & Marketing: 2/28/08 @ 12:00 PM in the Campus Center for Relay for Life photo., 2008 March 12; 25.1 MB 26
    - Media & Marketing: 3/3/08 @ 3:30 PM in the Blue Room at the Capital for photo of state authors., 2008 March 12; 155.9 MB 187
    - Media and Marketing: 2/28/08 @ 10:30 am UNH Atrium Presidential Scholar Educational Failr, 2008 March 13; 136.4 MB 96
    - University Events: Photo session: 3/18/08 from 4:30 to 6:30 PM @the Empire State Plaza for UAlbany Advocacy Day., 2008 March 18; 278.7 MB 233
    - University Events: Photo session: 3/18/08 from 4:30 to 6:30 PM @the Empire State Plaza for UAlbany Advocacy Day., 2008 March 18; 278.7 MB 233
    - President's Office: Photo session: 3/27/08 Congressman McNulty visit at the M.E. Grenander Dept of Special Collections and Archives (Science Library) at 9:30 am., 2008 March 27; 39.7 MB 91
    - Marketing Services: Photo session: 4/1/08 at 10 AM for defibrillator training for faculty/staff at the Campus Center Assembly Hall., 2008 April 1; 85.0 MB 50
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/5/08 @ 3:00 p.m. Relay for Life at the SEFCU Arena, 2008 April 5; 693.0 MB 368
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/7/08 The public effects of global climate change lecture from 3-4 p.m. at the East Campus. Dr. Julie Gerberding, 2008 April 7; 114.4 MB 64
    - University Events: 4/10/08 from 4 - 6 PM in D'Ambra Auditorium, Life Sciences Research Building for photo of Distinguished Professor Lecture and Reception featuring Dr. Arthur Applebee. Types of shots: candid shots during the lecture and during the first few minutes of the reception and a couple of posed group shots of the speakers/honoree., 2008 April 10; 352.5 MB 63
    - President's Office: Photo session: 4/14/08 from 12:30 pm to 1:30 in the atrium of University Hall for the brand launch., 2008 April 14; 130.2 MB 157
    - Media and Marketing: Photo session: 4/14/08 at 9:00 a.m. Fuel cell vehicle for Earth Day., 2008 April 16; 409.6 MB 87
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/2/08 at the Unitarian Cener, 405 Washington Ave. @ 1:00 p.m., 2008 April 16; 223.0 MB 115
    - Media and Marketing: Photo session: 4/14/08 at 9:00 a.m. Fuel cell vehicle for Earth Day., 2008 April 16; 409.6 MB 87
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/4/08 x-Factors conference, Life Sciences Bldg @ 9:30 a.m., 2008 April 17; 66.5 MB 33
    - Media & Marketing: 4/21/08 @ 1:45 pm, Rotunda of NanoFab 300 South for ceremony hosted by Senator Charles Schumer regarding a new collaborative initiative involving nanoscale education and research. Photo to used at center photo of UAlbany News page. Deadline for posting is 4/22/08 at 12 Noon. Please place in gpmr/UAlbany News folder., 2008 April 21; 91.0 MB 202
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/27/08 for Fountain Day Gallery, 2008 April 27; 393.5 MB 215
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/27/08 for Fountain Day Gallery, 2008 April 27; 393.5 MB 215
    - Dept. of Informatics: Photo session: 5/2/08 for the INF PhD Research Conference in the LSRB Auditorium., 2008 May 2; 101.0 MB 183
    - Alumni Programs: Photo session: 5/3/08 from 6:00 - 9:15 PM @ Holiday Inn Wolf Road for the annual Excellence Awards Gala., 2008 May 3; 150.5 MB 202
    - Media and Marketing: 4/15/08 @ 8 pm CC 375 National Society of Collegiate Scholars; Integity Day, 2008 May 5; 96.1 MB 56